Then suddenly, the sky above
cracked open
and a white beam of light reached
down into the earth
smiting the mother of harlots asunder
and setting the blood lake to a boil.
As the beast descended down into the
lake of fire
Isaac ascended towards the crack
in the sky
and as he flew he could see echoes of
his past before him.
He saw his mother mourning the
loss of her son.
He saw his father leaving them
without turning to say goodbye.
He saw his mother sleeping, and his
father taking money from her purse.
He heard the late night fights they
had that kept him up at night
and the guilt he felt for what he
believed he was causing.
He felt the pain in his stomach
during those sleepness nights
and saw his shadow in the closet
waiting for him.
As he rose, he felt his fears drop
from his body
his shame, his worry, pulled from
his being.
As he became lighter, his ascent
became faster.
He saw his one true companion
alive and well.
He saw his mother and father
together again, holding each other.
He felt his mother kissing him on
the head after he had said his prayers
and the comfort in knowing someone
was watching over him.
He saw his own birth
and the faces of his parents filled
with joy and optimism.
And then, he saw nothing.
Are you sure this is how you want
this story to end Isaac?
You're the one writing it, it
doesn't have to end this way.
Here. How about we tell it a
different way?
Maybe a happy ending?
- Okay daddy.
Good. Are you getting sleepy yet?
- Yeah.
Okay so... [clears throat]
Isaac and his parents lived in
a small house on the top of a hill...